If you don't already, you're going to want to install Unreal Engine.
You can do that by heading over to Unreal Engine Dotcom and just clicking the download button here.
This will take you to this page and you just won't want to download the epic game launcher.
Once you've downloaded the Epic Games launcher, it will look something like this.
You want to head over to library and here under engine versions, you want to just add a new engine
version so you can click here and select Unreal Engine version five and just install it.
Once you've downloaded Unreal Engine, you should be able to select the version you want to use here.
Make sure to select Unreal Engine version five.
Once you've downloaded Unreal Engine, add it to the Marketplace tab.
And here under search products, look for Paper Z.
No spaces.
We're going to be using this paper Z plugin to help us build our two D game.
Just head over and select this paper Z.
Then click install to engine and install it to Unreal Engine version five.
We're now ready to create our project.
We click launch.
This will open up the Unreal Project browser and you just want to head over to the Games tab and you'll
see set blank.
We're going to be creating a 2D game from complete scratch.
Then under project name, just cool this what you want to call your project.
I'm going to call this the action platformer.
And under project defaults, make sure that you set blueprint.
Then you can click create.
It should open up your Unreal Engine project and it should look something like this.
Before we get started, we're just going to enable the plugin because we're going to be using it later.
When we make our game to enable a plugin, simply head over to edit and go plugins.
Then here we want to search for Paper Z, the plugin that we installed and just check this little box
for.
Ask us if we want to restart our engine editor.
We need to just click restart now so it can restart with the plugin.